Thank you.
Alright.
You drank it all.
You,
and you,
go out and buy a bottle.
You too.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
And you.
Go.
Have you been
really annoyed with me lately?
I haven't.
Then swear.
If you are,
you'll never make any money.
Why should I swear?
Then you are.
Why?
It's my own problem.
The bag is heavy. Let me help.
No need.
It hurts me when you act like this suddenly.
Why does it hurt you?
I hate it when you're like this.
No.
Why are you so nice to everyone?
Why do you care
about everyone's feelings?
You're nice to
Yiyi,
and to Zhao Tianfang.
They're my colleagues
and clients. It's my job.
Fine.
Then what about my sister?
Why are you serving tea and water to my sister
and showing so much concern?
Because...
Because I have my difficulties.
Because you have ulterior motives,
right?
What ulterior motives?
I have my difficulties.
What difficulties?
You can't make anything up, can you?
Because I'm Golden Spiral.
The client who wrote the bad review
and got you fired was me.
And
I also ruined your sister's divorce photoshoot.
So I stayed to compensate her.
I supported her and treated her well
because I was afraid she'd tell you,
and you'd ignore me.
I...
I was also afraid it would affect our work.
I was worried about my year-end bonus.
So,
I want to have a good talk with you.
Talk?
Go ahead.
If you put money aside,
what do you want to talk about?
Can you put money aside?
True.
Wait for me.
Wait for you to do what?
Wait for you to write me a bad review?
What are you doing?
I'll carry it for you.
I don't need you to carry it. Give it to me.
You wrote a 2,000-word bad review.
How dare you even speak to me?
That was written by AI.
Written by AI?
You think you're so great?
Let's go.
What's so urgent
that you have to call me over in the middle of the night?
Keep it down.
Don't let her hear you.
Come in.
Xinyue,
here are the Honglai chicken feet you wanted.
They are super spicy.
Keep it down.
Come inside.
That's what happened.
After she found out I'm Golden Spiral,
she seems a bit angry.
Are you sure it's just a bit?
I'm so mad!
I found out later
that he's the jerk
who forced me to resign.
But he's been running around helping you lately.
At least he tried his best.
So,
she should forgive me.
Fifty percent?
Thirty percent?
At least fifteen percent?
In his dreams.
Besides,
if it weren't for my accidental push,
how could she have started her own business?
Just for this trivial matter,
she's acting like this with me.
I'm not angry about the Golden Spiral thing.
I just can't stand him as a person.
Besides, I didn't even provoke her.
I think I treat her pretty well,
always checking in on her and serving her drinks.
He doesn't understand women at all.
Why pretend to be a sweet guy?
He flirts with everyone.
You be the judge.
Is it a crime to be a good guy?
I really don't know what she's thinking.
Why are you crying?
Please don't cry.
Listen to that.
She's crying just because of this.
What's the fuss?
It's just from the spicy food.
Am I really that unforgivable?
How about
you schedule a time to have a good talk with her?
She's fuming right now.
If I ask her out,
she'll tear me to pieces.
True.
What are you holding in your hand?
Nothing, just a ring.
I won it in a lucky draw.
A lucky draw gave you such a beautiful women's ring?
You didn't buy it yourself, did you?
Then...
How is that possible?
Saving money is my lifelong priority.
How could I possibly
spend money on such impractical things?
It's obvious he did it on purpose.
Let me be clear.
Unless...
unless he
sincerely,
proactively,
and earnestly apologizes to me.
Otherwise, I definitely won't be nice to him.
Right.
Let's hold off for now.
When she softens up a bit,
you can have a good talk with her.
After all, it's better to make peace than hold grudges.
Okay.
Then we'll just wait and see.
Eat less.
You'll be bloated tomorrow.
This is so annoying.
Why give a women's ring for a raffle?
Then just give it to her.
Wouldn't it be nice to do her a favor?
Let's do that.
Morning.
How come it's you?
Then where is she?
Xinyue went out for an interview today.
Yiying went to the homestay.
So I'm filling in for the shift today.
Then why didn't you call me?
That difficult customer from last time
wrote a really long positive review for you two.
Now the shop is getting busier and busier.
By the way.
Xinyue said she arranged other work for you today.
Other work.
What kind of work is other work?
Here.
Welcome aboard.
Isn't this the guy who sells Honglai chicken feet?
Why did you bring him here?
Do we have any business dealings with him?
You mean Qin Fei?
His grandfather is going to sell chicken feet with Yuzhen next door,
so he was called here.
I am a minor shareholder at least.
Even if you want to hire someone new,
you should tell me first.
I did tell you.
I told you yesterday.
I said someone was coming for an interview this morning.
Look at him.
He is pleasing to the eye.
What a great value for money.
Li Xinyue, can you not be so superficial?
We are in the early stage of our startup.
You're expanding so blindly.
Just to see some muscles,
you're spending thousands more a month.
Who exactly is superficial between us?
You,
Mr. Qin.
I...
I remember you.
That day, you and Xinyue
came to our stall to buy chicken feet.
My name is Qin Fei.
Are you done yet?
Dawdling.
I heard you're hiring here.
I thought I'd recommend myself.
At least it's an easy job.
Listen to him.
He's here to slack off.
Can we hire this kind of employee?
Is he cost-effective?
Mr. Qin, it's like this.
What we're looking for is a driver
to pick up clients or move goods.
If you're looking for a relaxing job,
I'm afraid you're not suitable for this.
Well,
I rest when I'm free and work when there's a task.
Besides,
I don't need a salary.
Just give me food.
Yiyi.
Get the contract from the second drawer.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
Your place already has Lin Yiyi,
me, and you.
Where do you have a spare room for anyone else?
I'll live on my own.
My family owns three buildings
just for collecting rent.
I heard Mr. Tang also works here.
He's my tenant.
He lives right across from me.
Welcome aboard.
Can you give me a ride later?
A client said yesterday
that they want me to help find a shop or something.
Zhang Yang, stay here and watch the shop.